shopaccino.com 2015-06-20

# Shopaccino Privacy Policy

When you visit this website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis, and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our website.

* #### Personal information you choose to provide

  * **Registration Information:**  
When you register for subscription or any of our services / newsletters you will provide us with information about yourself.
  * **Email Information:**  
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same level of protection for electronic communications as we do for information received by mail and telephone.
  * **Communication with You:**  
Registration or correspondence with us via email constitutes a commercial relationship and implies consent for us to communicate with you regarding our services. We promise to only send you information deemed relevant to our commercial relationship and any email communication you may receive from us highlighting our services, special offers or promotions will include an opt out or unsubscribe feature.

* #### Website use details

Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” and web server log files to collect information about how our website is used. Information gathered through cookies and web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our website, and the websites visited just before and just after our website.

* #### Saving of collected information

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our website, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). When credit card details are collected, we simply pass them on in order to be processed as required. We never permanently store complete credit card details.  
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.

* #### Using of collected information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it through your Shopaccino admin store account.

* #### How we use your information provided by you to us?

We use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, provision of services, monitoring the use of services, marketing and promotional efforts, improvement of our content and service offerings, and customization of our website’s content, layout, services and other lawful purposes. These activities improve our website and enable us to better tailor it to meet your needs.  
Furthermore, such information may be shared with others on an aggregate basis. Personally identifiable information or business information will not be shared with parties except as required by law.  
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our website, new services, and special offers we think you will find valuable. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers.

* #### How we use information collected by cookies? 

As you visit and browse our website, the website uses cookies to differentiate you from other users. In some cases, we also use cookies to prevent you from having to log in more than is necessary for security. Cookies, in conjunction with our web server’s log files, allow us to calculate the aggregate number of people visiting our website and which parts of the site are most popular. This helps us gather feedback to constantly improve our website and better serve our clients. Cookies do not allow us to gather any personal information about you and we do not intentionally store any personal information that your browser provided to us in your cookies.

* #### IP addresses

Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as traffic data so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you.

* #### Information sharing

We do not share, sell, lend or lease any of the information that uniquely identify a subscriber (such as email addresses or personal details) with anyone except to the extent it is necessary to process transactions or provide services that you have requested.

* #### Legally Compelled disclosure of information

We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights. We may also disclose account information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Terms of Service or to protect the safety of our users and the Public.

* #### Other websites connected to our website

We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites connected to or from our web site or the information or content contained therein. Often links to other websites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our website.  
Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link on our website, is subject to that website’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

* #### Your consent

By using our website you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice.

* #### Our commitment to data security

Please note that your information will be stored and processed on our computers in India. The laws on holding personal data in India may be less stringent than the laws of your country of residence or citizenship. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

* #### Choices

Shopaccino website allows visitors to unsubscribe so that they will not receive future messages and emails. After unsubscribing we will discontinue sending the particular messages as soon as technically feasible.

* #### Acquisition or change in ownership 

In the event that the website (or a substantial portion of its assets) is acquired, your information would be considered part of those assets, and may be part of those assets that are transferred.

* #### Policy changes or updates

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when changes are made to this privacy policy, we will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

Shopaccino is a product of I Solution Microsystems Private Limited (CIN: U72200RJ2009PTC030152)
